Guide to the Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Departmental Files, 1940-1960; Series I
  - 1952-1953
    - American Public Health Association
      - Committee on Administrative Practice, 1952-1953 (Box 153, Folder 1674-1676)
      - Annual Meeting, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1677)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1678)
    - American Public Health Association
      - Sanitation project, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1679)
      - Subcommittee on Medical Care of the Committee on Administrative Practice, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1680)
      - Subcommittee on Mental Hygiene, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1681)
      - Committee on Health Education, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1682)
      - Subcommittee on Chronic Disease and Rehabilitation, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1683)
    - American Red Cross - National, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1684)
    - American Social Hygiene Association, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1685)
    - American Heart Association, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1686)
    - Association of Schools of Public Health, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1687-1688)
    - California, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1689)
    - Columbia, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1690)
    - Harvard, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1691)
    - Johns Hopkins, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1692)
    - Michigan, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 1693)
    - Minnesota, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1694)
    - North Carolina, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1695)
    - Toronto, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1696)
    - Pittsburgh, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1697)
    - Connecticut Cancer Society, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1698)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1699)
    - Public Health Merit Badge Booklet Carbon, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1700)
    - Connecticut Hospital Association, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1702)
    - Connecticut Diabetes Association, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1703)
    - Connecticut State Department of Health, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1704)
    - Commissioner, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1705)
    - Preventable diseases, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1706)
    - Vital statistics, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1707)
    - Venereal disease, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 1708)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1709)
    - Connecticut State Public Health Council, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1710)
    - State of Connecticut Commission on Alcoholism, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1711)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1712)
    - Connecticut Medical Service, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1713)
    - Hawaii, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1714-1715)
    - Institute of Inter-American Affairs, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1716)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1720)
    - National Association for Mental Hygiene Incorporated, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1721)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1722)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis New Haven Chapter, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1723)
    - National Health Council, 1952-1953 (Box 156, Folder 1724)
    - National Health Council, 1952-1953 (Box 157, Folder 1725-1728)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1952-1953 (Box 157, Folder 1729-1730)
    - National Publicity Council, 1952-1953 (Box 157, Folder 1731)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1952-1953 (Box 157, Folder 1732)
    - National Research Council, 1952-1953 (Box 158, Folder 1733)
    - National Sanitation Foundation, 1952-1953 (Box 158, Folder 1734)
    - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1952-1953 (Box 158, Folder 1735-1738)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1952-1953 (Box 158, Folder 1739)
    - Connecticut Tuberculosis Association, 1952-1953 (Box 159, Folder 1740-1741)
    - New Haven Tuberculosis Association, 1952-1953 (Box 159, Folder 1742)
    - New Haven Board of Health, 1952-1953 (Box 159, Folder 1743)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1952-1953 (Box 159, Folder 1744)
    - Rheumatic Fever and Cardiac Program, 1952-1953 (Box 159, Folder 1745)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1952-1953 (Box 159, Folder 1746-1747)
    - New Haven Hospital, 1952-1953 (Box 159, Folder 1749)
    - Visiting Nurse Association of New Haven, 1952-1953 (Box 159, Folder 1751)
    - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1753)
    - United States Army, 1952-1953 (Box 160, Folder 1754)
    - United States Navy, 1952-1953 (Box 160, Folder 1755)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1952-1953 (Box 160, Folder 1756-1760)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1761)
    - Venereal Disease Study, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1762)
    - Grant CS-545(C2) Cohart United States Public Health Service, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1763)
    - Mental hygiene, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1764)
    - Grant RG-2307-Gelperin (pending), 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1765)
    - Grant 1754(R) Gelperin, United States Public Health Service, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1767)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1768)
    - Division of International Health, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1769)
    - Health Department (City, County, State), 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1770-1772)
    - Young Men's Christian Association, Young Women"s Christian Association, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1773)
    - Community Chests and Councils, Incorporated, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 1774)
    - National Budget Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 162, Folder 1776)
    - National Budget Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 162, Folder 1777-1779)
    - National Dairy Council, 1952-1953 (Box 162, Folder 1780)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1952-1953 (Box 162, Folder 1781)
    - New England Health Institute, 1952-1953 (Box 162, Folder 1782)
    - World Health Organization, 1952-1953 (Box 162, Folder 1783-1784)
  - 1953-1954
    - A General, 1953-1954 (Box 163, Folder 1785-1787)
    - Association for Retarded Children of Greater New Haven, 1953-1954 (Box 163, Folder 1788)
    - B General, 1953-1954 (Box 163, Folder 1789-1791)
    - Andre Blumenthal, 1953-1954 (Box 164, Folder 1792)
    - C General, 1953-1954 (Box 164, Folder 1793-1796)
    - China, 1953-1954 (Box 164, Folder 1797)
    - Committee on School Health Program, 1953 (Box 164, Folder 1798)
    - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China (Taiwan trip), 1953-1954 (Box 164, Folder 1799)
    - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China (Taiwan trip), 1953-1954 (Box 165, Folder 1800-1802)
    - Civil Defense: general, 1953-1954 (Box 165, Folder 1803)
    - Civil Defense: local, state and national, 1953-1954 (Box 165, Folder 1804)
    - Cleveland Health Museum, 1953-1954 (Box 165, Folder 1805)
    - Commission for the Chronically III, Aged and Infirm, 1953-1954 (Box 165, Folder 1806-1807)
    - Commission on Careers in Nursing, 1953-1954 (Box 165, Folder 1808)
    - Connecticut Health League, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1809)
    - Connecticut Nutrition Council, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1810)
    - Connecticut Regional Blood Program, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1811)
    - Connecticut Trudeau Society, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1812)
    - D General, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1813)
    - Dental Clinic Society of New Haven, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1814)
    - E General, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1815)
    - F General, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1816)
    - Fellowships, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1817)
    - G General, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 1818)
    - G General, 1953-1954 (Box 167, Folder 1819)
    - H General, 1953-1954 (Box 167, Folder 1820)
    - Health Information Foundation (Box 167, Folder 1821-1823)
    - Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York, 1953-1954 (Box 167, Folder 1824)
    - Human Relations Area Files, Incorporated, 1953-1954 (Box 167, Folder 1825)
    - Health Councils, 1953-1954 (Box 167, Folder 1826)
    - I General, 1953-1954 (Box 168, Folder 1827)
    - Inventory, 1953-1954 (Box 168, Folder 1828-1829)
    - J General, 1953-1954 (Box 168, Folder 1830)
    - K General, 1953-1954 (Box 168, Folder 1831)
    - L General, 1953-1954 (Box 168, Folder 1832)
    - Lee, Sik Siang, 1953-1954 (Box 168, Folder 1833)
    - M General, 1953-1954 (Box 168, Folder 1834-1836)
    - M General, 1953-1954 (Box 169, Folder 1837)
    - Joseph W. Mountain Memorial, 1953-1954 (Box 169, Folder 1838)
    - N General, 1953-1954 (Box 169, Folder 1839-1842)
    - N General, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1843)
    - New Canaan, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1844)
    - New England Public Health Institute, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1845)
    - O General, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1846)
    - P General, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1847-1848)
    - R General, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1849)
    - Rhode Island Medical Society, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1850)
    - S General, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1851)
    - Society of Public Health Educators, 1953-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1852)
    - Index of lantern slides, undated (Box 171, Folder 1853)
    - T General, 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1854)
    - U General, 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1855)
    - V General, 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1856)
    - Visitors, 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1857)
    - Veterans' Administration Hospital of West Haven, 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1858)
    - W General, 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1859)
    - Winslow, C.E.A., 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1860-1861)
    - C.E.A. Winslow - lectureship, 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1862)
    - Winslow, C.E.A. - survey report, 1953-1954 (Box 172, Folder 1863)
    - Wisconsin Anti-Tuberculosis Association, 1953 (Box 172, Folder 1864)
    - Yale Calendar, 1953 (Box 172, Folder 1865)
    - Yale University Department of Public Health Bursary Schedules, 1953-1954 (Box 172, Folder 1866)
    - Yale University: general, 1953-1954 (Box 172, Folder 1867-1868)
    - Yale Study of Alcohol Studies, 1953-1954 (Box 172, Folder 1869)
    - Yale Chapter of Sigma XI, 1953-1954 (Box 172, Folder 1870)
    - Yale Committee on Statistics, 1953-1954 (Box 172, Folder 1871)
    - Yale Medical Society, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1872)
    - Yale News Bureau, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1873)
    - Z General, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1874)
    - Hospital Administration, 1950-1952, 1950-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1875-1879)
    - G.R. Cowgill - Nutrition, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1880)
    - G.H. Dession: Law, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1881)
    - J.R. Paul, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1882)
    - Institute of Occupational Medicine and Hygiene, 1953-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1883)
    - Institute of Occupational Medicine and Hygiene, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 1884-1887)
    - P.B. Cowels - Bacteriology, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 1888)
    - Eckka Gordon - Social Service, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 1889)
    - Charles C. Wilson - School Health Education, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 1890)
    - Joint Committee of Health Problems in Education, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 1891)
    - Other staff members, 1950-1952 (Box 174, Folder 1892-1893)
    - Howard Stewart Pfirman, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 1894)
    - Jonas N. Miller, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 1897)
    - Joseph K. Hill, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1898)
    - Milton I. Roemer, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1899)
    - Harry Auerbach, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1900)
    - Emily Myrtile Smith, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1901)
    - Howard P. Cadwell, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1902)
    - Frances Cord, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1903)
    - Ann Switzer, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1904)
    - Vaughn Smith, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1905)
    - Virginia Marr, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1906)
    - Doris Johnson, 1952-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1907)
    - Charlotte F. Muller, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1908)
    - Edward Cuyler Hammond, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1909)
    - Alexander Neuwirth, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1910)
    - Nathan Kramer, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1911)
    - Albert S. Gray, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1912)
    - Former staff members, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1913)
    - Staff, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1914)
    - Staff minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1915)
    - Other public health fields, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1916)
    - Housing, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1917)
    - Motion pictures, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1918)
    - Nursing, 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1919)
    - Tuberculosis, 1953 (Box 175, Folder 1920)
    - President's office, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1921)
    - Director of Medical Affairs, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1922)
    - Provost's office, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1923)
    - Treasurer's office, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1924)
    - Budget, 1953-1654 (Box 176, Folder 1925)
    - Recommendations for appointment, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1926)
    - Dean: Graduate School, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1927)
    - Assistant Dean: Graduate School, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1928)
    - Registrar - Graduate School, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1929)
    - Dean: Medical School, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1930)
    - Assistant Dean: Medical school, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1931)
    - Committee of Clinical Science and Practice, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1932)
    - Executive Secretary: Medical School, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1933)
    - Committee on Admissions: Medical School, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1934)
    - Stanley H. Davis: Business office, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1935)
    - Blue Cross, 1954-1955 (Box 176, Folder 1936)
    - Department of Education: Yale, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1937)
    - Yale School of Nursing, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1938)
    - University Library, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 1939)
    - Yale Medical Library, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1940-1941)
    - Yale Historical Library, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1942)
    - Alumni Association of Yale, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1943)
    - Delta Omega, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1944)
    - Secretary - Yale University, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1945)
    - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1946)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1947)
    - Executive Committee minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1948)
    - Department of University Health, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1949)
    - Department of Psychiatry and Mental Hygiene, 1953-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1950)
    - Bishop Museum Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1951)
    - Pacific Science Council Secretariat, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1952)
    - Department of University Health, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1953)
    - Candidates for jobs, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1954)
    - Accreditation plan, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1955)
    - Committee on Admissions Department, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1956)
    - Newsletter, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1957)
    - Publishers, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1958-1959)
    - Recommendations for jobs, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1960)
    - Requests for candidates for jobs, 1953-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1961-1962)
    - Visiting lecturers, 1953-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1963)
    - Field trips, 1953-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1964)
    - Annual reports, 1953-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1965)
    - Legislation, Federal Bills, 1953-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1966)
    - Vital statistics, 1953-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1967)
    - Secretarial staff, 1953-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1968-1970)
    - Department of Public Health: Alumni News, 1953-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1971)
    - Request for article on home accident prevention from Dr. Schwinger of Germany, 1954 (Box 180, Folder 1972)
    - Ladies Aid, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1973)
    - American Cancer Society, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1974)
    - American Cancer Society (Massachusetts and other Divisions), 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1975)
    - Governor's folder: State of Connecticut, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1976)
    - Connecticut Heart Association, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1977)
    - New Haven Heart Association, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1978)
    - American Dental Association, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1979)
    - American Epidemiological Society, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1980)
    - American Medical Association, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1981)
    - American Public Health Association, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1982-1984)
      - American Journal of Public Health, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1985)
      - Committee on State and Local Health Administration, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1986)
      - Committee on Eligibility, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1987)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1988)
      - Committee on Administrative Practice, 1953-1954 (Box 181, Folder 1989-1994)
      - Committee on Administrative Practice, 1953-1954 (Box 182, Folder 1995-1996)
      - Annual meeting, 1953-1954 (Box 182, Folder 1997)
      - Annual meeting, Southern Branch, 1953-1954 (Box 182, Folder 1998)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1953-1954 (Box 182, Folder 1999)
    - American Public Health Association
      - Sanitation project, 1953-1954 (Box 182, Folder 2000)
      - Sub-committee on Medical care, 1953-1954 (Box 182, Folder 2001)
      - Committee on Health Education, 1953-1954 (Box 182, Folder 2002)
      - Sub-committee on Chronic Disease and Rehabilitation, 1953-1954 (Box 183, Folder 2003)
    - American Red Cross - National, 1953-1954 (Box 183, Folder 2004)
    - American Red Cross - New Haven Chapter, 1953-1954 (Box 183, Folder 2005)
    - American Social Hygiene Association, 1953-1954 (Box 183, Folder 2006)
    - American Heart Association, 1953-1954 (Box 183, Folder 2007-2011)
    - American Heart Association, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2012)
    - Association of Schools of Public Health, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2013)
    - California, University of, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2014)
    - Columbia University, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2015)
    - Harvard school of Public Health, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2016)
    - Johns Hopkins, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2017)
    - Michigan, University of, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2018)
    - Minnesota, University of, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2019)
    - North Carolina, University of, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2020)
    - Toronto, University of, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2021)
    - Pittsburgh, University of, 1953-1954 (Box 184, Folder 2022)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1953-1954 (Box 185, Folder 2023-2024)
    - Committee on State Health Administration, 1953-1954 (Box 185, Folder 2025)
    - Connecticut Cancer Society, 1953-1954 (Box 185, Folder 2027)
    - Connecticut Hospital Association, 1953-1954 (Box 185, Folder 2028)
    - Connecticut Diabetes Association, 1953-1954 (Box 185, Folder 2029)
    - Connecticut Mental Health Association, 1953-1954 (Box 185, Folder 2030)
    - New Haven Mental Hygiene Association, 1953-1954 (Box 185, Folder 2031)
    - Connecticut State Department of Health, 1953-1954 (Box 185, Folder 2032-2033)
    - Connecticut State Department of Health, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2034-2035)
      - Commissioner, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2036)
    - Bureau of Preventable Diseases, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2037)
    - Venereal diseases, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2038)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2039)
    - Connecticut State Public Health Commission, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2040-2041)
    - Connecticut State Department of Education, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2042)
    - State of Connecticut: Commission on Alcoholism, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2043)
    - Connecticut Medical Advisory Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2044)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2045)
    - Connecticut State Department of Finance and Control, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2046)
    - Connecticut State: Office of the Comptroller, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2047)
    - Connecticut State: Medical Journal, 1953-1954 (Box 186, Folder 2048)
    - Connecticut Advisory Council on School, 1954-1955 (Box 187, Folder 2049)
    - Hawaii, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 2050)
    - Institute on Inter-American Affairs, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 2051)
    - Maternity Center Association, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 2053)
    - National Association of Housing, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 2055)
    - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, Incorporated, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 2056)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 2057)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, New Haven Chapter, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 2058)
    - National Health Council, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 2059-2060)
    - National Health Council, 1953-1954 (Box 188, Folder 2061-2063)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1953-1954 (Box 188, Folder 2064-2065)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1953-1954 (Box 189, Folder 2066-2067)
    - National Publicity Council, 1953-1954 (Box 189, Folder 2068)
    - National Citizens Committee for Educational Television, 1953-1954 (Box 189, Folder 2069-2070)
    - National Research Council, 1953-1954 (Box 189, Folder 2071)
    - National Sanitation Foundation, 1953-1954 (Box 189, Folder 2072)
    - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1953-1954 (Box 190, Folder 2073-2074)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1953-1954 (Box 190, Folder 2075)
    - Connecticut Tuberculosis Association, 1953-1954 (Box 190, Folder 2076)
    - New Haven Area Tuberculosis and Health Association, 1953-1954 (Box 190, Folder 2077)
    - New Haven Board of Health, 1953-1954 (Box 190, Folder 2078)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1953-1954 (Box 190, Folder 2079)
    - Rheumatic Fever and Heart Diseases, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2080)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies: Mental Health Studies, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2081)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2082-2083)
    - Grace-New Haven Community Hospital, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2084)
    - New Haven Junior League, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2085)
    - Visiting Nurse Association of New Haven, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2086)
    - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2088)
    - United States Army, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2089)
    - Navy, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2090)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1953-1954 (Box 191, Folder 2091-2092)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2093)
    - Venereal Disease Study, 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2094)
    - Mental hygiene, 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2095)
    - Grant RG-1072(C) Gilperin-Mood: United States Public Health Service, 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2096)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2098)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2099)
    - United States Public Health Service: Division of International Health, 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2100)
    - Department oh Health, Education and Welfare, 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2101-2103)
    - Health Department (City, County and State), 1953-1954 (Box 192, Folder 2104)
    - Health Department (City, County and State), 1953-1954 (Box 193, Folder 2105-2107)
    - Health Department: New York State, 1953-1954 (Box 193, Folder 2108)
    - New York City Health Department, 1953-1954 (Box 193, Folder 2109)
    - Young Men"s Christian Association Young Women"s Christian Association, 1953-1954 (Box 193, Folder 2110)
    - Communities Chests and Councils of America, 1953-1954 (Box 193, Folder 2111-2112)
    - National Budget and Quota Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 194, Folder 2113-2118)
    - National Budget and Quota Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 194, Folder 2119)
    - National Dairy Council, 1953-1954 (Box 194, Folder 2121)
    - National Education Association, 1953-1954 (Box 194, Folder 2122)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1953-1954 (Box 194, Folder 2123)